Long ago, an already extraordinary
man wished for further power.
This man could soar like
a bird, swim like a fish,
breathe like a tree, and
move like a winding stream.
But sunlight spelled his doom,
so he created a stone mask.
One day, he would face
the sun without fear.
And then, the world would be his.
Vertigo, please tell me
cars fell into the lava.
I'm still alive. All right.
Must create armor.
Something like a clam.
Or a crab, a bony shell.
Yes, make me impervious!
It's not enough!
You dummy, that's lava!
It's a thousand degrees in there!
Now burn to a crisp, you cocky bastard!
Ouch!
Yes!
That did it!
Finally!
Kars was the last of them!
The Pillar Men are defeated!
The shock of his demise
triggered an eruption!
Let's get to safety before we
celebrate further! Good call!
Hang on tight, alright?
Music to my ears.
You perform that aria perfectly.
I've so longed to hear you sing it, Jojo!
Kars, you're alive!
A bit of his shell!
Inorganic, but of course!
Kars first covered himself in a
substance, not unlike a crab shell.
However, it was still organic.
It wasn't up to the task.
Faced with the heat of the
lava, it burned away instantly.
Luckily for Kars, he had the idea
to create a second layer of armor,
made of an unlikely
substance, mere air bubbles.
The bubbles maintained a pocket of air
between Kars' body and the lethal heat.
As the outer layer burned
away with each passing second,
But more bubbles worked their
way outward to replace them,
maintaining a perfect equilibrium.
Kars had the moments he needed to escape.
The Earth gave birth to life.
But now,
horror of horrors, Kars, a creature of the
Earth, has conquered the planet itself!
Eons ago,
long before man first thought to
chronicle his deeds, A group of creatures,
like us but not, evolved
alongside humanity.
The sun was lethal to them,
so they lived out their
lives under the cool
glow of the moon and in
their subterranean cities.
Even without the sun's sustaining rays,
they endured far longer than their human
rivals by feeding on other living things.
To humans that knew of their existence,
they were revered as gods or demons.
Their numbers were small, as
few died and children were rare.
In all things, they
maintained a vital balance.
They knew no strife and lived
in peace with one another.
But then, a man of great pride
and ambition was born among them.
Strength is hidden within this body,
talents we cannot but dream of.
I shall be the one to unlock them.
To that end, he created a stone mask.
The mask granted him unheralded power,
but at a terrible, ravenous cost.
To survive, he had to consume
life at a dizzying rate.
If left unchecked, he would eventually
devour every living thing on Earth.
His brethren began to fear the mask, as
well as the gifted soul who created it.
His very existence is a threat!
There is no place for one
such as him in this world.
We have to wipe out his evil.
Look at you fools.
Don't you want to have
dominion over the sun?
To stand in ascendance over all life?
To purge your fears and
reign forever as gods?
If not, then die.
The Iconoclast brazenly
slaughtered his brethren,
even killing the parents
who had given him life.
He and his sole ally
took the two surviving
infants and left the scene of the carnage.
They set off in search of ultimate power,
a journey of continents
and centuries alike.
And now, 10,000 years later, that
power was in his hands at last.
He's a god this tyrant has become a deity
and against such a foe
there is nothing that
we can do we must submit
or perish
hear that
i think jojo is trying
to tell me something
Hamon overdrive!
What? Hamon?
Did you say Hamon overdrive?
Jojo!
No, how?
My leg, it's melting away!
This is impossible!
Melting?
You don't mean to say!
It can't be!
Denial will get you nowhere, my friend.
Hamon did that!
I conquered the sun itself.
What makes you think that something
like Hamon was somehow beyond my reach?
I just...
Not only is Hamon at my disposal,
but it seems that mine is
hundreds of times more potent.
My god!
That's much stronger than Jojo's!
It's as though he brushed
his knee against the sun!
His flesh is liquefying and
vaporizing before his very eyes.
I wonder, how do you like the
taste of your own medicine?
Hmm, a very articulate reply.
I suppose it's time to put
you out of your misery.
Jojo!
This is it.
I'm going to die here.
This is the end.
Jojo accepted his impending demise calmly.
He felt no fear, no pain,
no regret at his plight.
I did all I could, he told himself.
As the epitome of evil
loomed over Jojo in triumph,
he watched his dying self
with perfect clarity.
Stroheim felt much the same.
Unable to move, he knew what snake prey
feels like as it stares into Oblivion's maw.
The power in a breath.
To think I will annihilate a practitioner
of Hamon with his own discipline.
Surely you can appreciate
the irony in that.
Ha... more?
Stronger than mine has ever been.
Let me be the first to
welcome you into oblivion!
Wait, Harmon?
What the...
the red stone?
The Red Stone of Asia!
But why did Jojo brandish it
at Kars in that final moment?
Even he had no idea!
As if by instinct,
he lunged the stone towards the
approaching Hamon to which it gravitated.
Saga!
Now, in a moment devoid of hope,
Jojo's body did the one thing
that could save his life!
Having survived Karr's coup de Crazy,
his will to live sprang into action.
Yes, the red stone amplifies Hamon!
Fueled by the magnified blast of Hamon,
the volcano's fury reaches
the breaking point.
It erupts!
What?
They've blasted into the sky!
The force is strong, like
nothing I've ever known!
Do you really think a little eruption
will be enough to conquer the likes of me?
I'll just fly my way to safety.
Enjoy the fruits of your folly, Jojo!
Who's laughing now, huh?
Let me guess.
You're gonna say, did you
plan this too, Jojo? Tell me.
How do you always know?
For a moment, Kars was distracted by
Jojo's arm and his cocky attitude.
That moment was all it took.
Scalding rocks he didn't see coming launched
him even higher into the stratosphere!
Did you plan this too, Jojo? Tell me!
Why are you even asking?
I set the trap and you
walked right into it!
All of this went down like clockwork!
I just got lucky, but thinking I
outsmarted him will drive cars nuts!
At that moment,
the rocks launched by the volcano's
eruption reached escape velocity.
Kars was the perfect being!
Nothing on Earth could kill him!
But, just then, he was blasted
into the vacuum of space!
No!
Damn you!
It's over.
Granny, and Stroheim, old Speedwagon,
Smoky, and Lisa Lisa.
Everyone, goodbye.
No.
JoJo!
Von Stroheim made it back to
the others eight hours later,
whereupon he told them this sad news.
No! No!
Don't panic!
Just find the Earth!
I'll use air to change my trajectory.
Once I'm back on solid ground,
I will tear that boy apart!
No!
It's not working!
I'm freezing!
The air is freezing around me.
The moment it comes out of the jets!
It turns to ice.
I can't change my path.
I can't move.
So ended Kars?
Last and greatest of the Pillar Men.
His body turned hard as rock, and he
floated through space for the rest of time,
never to return.
He wished for death, but there
was nothing out there to kill him.
The spark of thought within
him went dim, and then silent.
We commend his soul unto the
heavenly father though his life
on earth has ended far too
soon he lives in grace with you
comfort those he leaves behind Oh
God and let them know your peace
Goodbye, Jojo I didn't know you for too
long couldn't have been more than six months
don't matter even though
you're gone I'm your friend
forever
Come, Iran.
It won't do to catch cold.
Let's get you home.
Just a bit longer.
Guess who?
What gives, fellas?
I finally make it to New York, and
nobody was there to pick me up!
Then, I got word you were all at a
funeral, so I decided to crash it.
Hey, Lisa Lisa!
Guess you healed up pretty well, huh?
Messina, good to see you, too.
New hand works well.
Though I've been meaning
to ask Stroheim if he can
jazz it up with a few
gadgets or tools or whatnot.
I guess that's right out
with us fighting Germany.
Hey, now!
You leave these mourners alone!
This is a funeral!
Show some respect, you own...
Oh, so I'm oaf, am I?
You need a lesson in manners,
and I'm glad to apply!
All right, calm down.
Let's not be hasty.
I'm sure you didn't mean
nothing by it. No way.
I'm talking to you, big
guy! You'd better...
Back off, man!
I'm just trying to catch up
with my family and friends.
JoJo!
You're telling me JoJo's alive?! Huh?
Yeah, of course.
Wait, what's this about?
You're all staring as
though you've seen a ghost.
I know it's a funeral, and uh-huh.
What the?
What's my name doing on there?
I'm alive and well!
Wait, this funeral was for me?
Jojo!
You're still recovering, you big silly.
Don't run off in the rain like that.
Here, take this.
Hey, that girl is Suzy Q.
And that ring looks like a...
Are you telling me you don't
know that we got married?
You got married?
Isn't it crazy?
Just think about it.
I'm officially Mrs.
Joseph Joestar. Goodness.
It makes me blush.
Wait a second here.
Suzy Q, something about this doesn't
feel right and I want to know what.
The rock I was on fell into
the ocean and me along with it.
A fishing boat picked me up.
So far, so good.
You nursed me back to health in Venice
for two weeks, and we tied the knot.
So why did they all think I was dead?
You never sent that telegram
like I asked, did you?
Uh, I don't really know.
To me, that sounds like no.
Uh, now, now, let's not
get all clicky fingers.
I never sent it!
I'm sorry, JoJo!
Ah! Suzy Q!
What the hell?
You had one job, woman! One job!
Ah!
JoJo came back to us all!
Stop it!
I said I was sorry! Sorry?
They thought I was dead!
JoJo.
Soon after, Lisa Lisa, a .k .a.
Elizabeth Joestar, told JoJo
that she was his mother.
they moved to America.
In 1948, she found love again and
married a Hollywood screenwriter.
Iran Joestar continued
her work as a teacher.
In 1950, she died
peacefully at the age of 81,
surrounded by family and
friends who loved her.
Robert E .O.
Speedwagon continued to pour his
energy into philanthropic research,
helping to further science and
medicine in countless ways.
He died in 1952 of a heart
attack at 89 years of age.
A lifelong bachelor, he
left no family behind.
Smokey Brown went on to work his way through
college, majoring in political science.
Later, he became the first black mayor
of a city in his home state of Georgia.
Major Rudolph von Stroheim
would never see Jojo
again he died in 1943 at
the battle of Stalingrad.
A fearsome example of
the German science he'd
always championed our
technology is the greatest.
And so the years flowed
by to a new generation.
And as for JoJo...
Oh, breaking the leg, huh?
Sorry about that.
You should watch where you're going.
You wouldn't want a
broken bone at your age.
You're right.
How careless of me.
I guess this is a case
of live and learn. Hmm?
Hey, wait a sec.
You're Japanese, aren't
you? I am. Why do you ask?
In that case, watch your damn bag!
My only daughter has been married
to a Japanese man for over 20 years.
Fell in love on the other side of
the world and never came home again.
Her son rarely gets to
see his own grandfather.
That's why I'll never
forgive the Japanese.
Then again, they make
some rather nifty gadgets.
Yeah, that's true, we're gonna
get yasura no Seiko o tsuka!
Dario ni ta omoi ga, Mariah no Cairo ko?
Like a burning stone,
hot-suk like a burning stone.
Ketsu Mega ni kizamareta yunan ni.
Uki no ni kei wa koi no kizuna.
Niigiri shimete.
All right, it's finally
time to haul it up.
Oh, man.
What do you think's inside it, you guys?
A hundred-year-old chest like that?
It could be anything.
Come on, let's open that bad boy.